[
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "pretext": "Take a quick break from learning katakana by taking this short quiz! But first, let’s recap:"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "T",
    "options": ["Ta – タ", "Chi – チ", "Tsu – ツ", "Te – テ", "To – ト"]
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "N",
    "options": ["Na – ナ", "Ni – ニ", "Nu – ヌ", "Ne – ネ", "No – ノ"]
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "H",
    "options": ["Ha – ハ", "Hi – ヒ", "Hu – フ", "He – ヘ", "Ho – ホ"]
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Chi",
    "options": ["ハ", "チ", "ツ", "テ"],
    "answer": "チ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Ha",
    "options": ["ホ", "フ", "ヘ", "ハ"],
    "answer": "ハ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Ho",
    "options": ["ノ", "ホ", "ナ", "ヒ"],
    "answer": "ホ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Ne",
    "options": ["ネ", "ノ", "ナ", "ニ"],
    "answer": "ネ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "No",
    "options": ["ト", "ツ", "ノ", "ナ"],
    "answer": "ノ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Tsu",
    "options": ["テ", "タ", "ナ", "ツ"],
    "answer": "ツ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Ni",
    "options": ["ハ", "ニ", "チ", "ツ"],
    "answer": "ニ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Na",
    "options": ["ノ", "ヌ", "フ", "ナ"],
    "answer": "ナ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Hu",
    "options": ["フ", "ハ", "ヘ", "ヒ"],
    "answer": "フ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "He",
    "options": ["ホ", "ノ", "ヘ", "ト"],
    "answer": "ヘ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Ta",
    "options": ["タ", "テ", "チ", "ト"],
    "answer": "タ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Te",
    "options": ["ヘ", "ホ", "テ", "タ"],
    "answer": "テ"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "To",
    "options": ["ホ", "ト", "ナ", "ヌ"],
    "answer": "ト"
  },
  {
    "type": "mc",
    "prompt": "Nu",
    "options": ["ネ", "ナ", "ヌ", "タ"],
    "answer": "ヌ"
  },
  {"type": "mc", "prompt": "Hi", "options": ["ヒ", "ホ", "ハ", "ノ"], "answer": "ヒ"}
]